sitemapx.com 2016-03-11

# Sitemap X Privacy Policy

We at SitemapX.com affirm our commitment to respecting and protecting your online privacy. his includes your need and your right to know our management of the information you share with us, such as for what purposes we collect the information and how it is collected and processed. 

By accessing this website, and registering as a member, you are consenting to the way your information is collected and used, as described within this Privacy Policy. 

In return, SitemapX.com gives the commitment that we will use the personal data you provide only in ways that comply with the following Privacy Policy. 

## The collection of information 

Every time you log on to our site, your IP (Internet Protocol) address registers on our servers. Your IP address reveals no information other than the number assigned to you. We do not use this technology to get any personal data without your knowledge or against your free will (i.e., automatically recording e-mail addresses of visitors). Nor do we use it for any purpose other than helping us monitor traffic on our website, or (in case of criminal activity or misuse of our information) cooperating with law enforcement. 

## Cookies

SitemapX.com may send "cookies" to your computer. Cookies are fragments of data sent through the web server and stored in your hard drive. Cookies can't read the files stored in your computer, nor can they gather information. The purpose of cookies is just to monitor the traffic on the site, so we know which pages you have visited or customized, making it easier for you to download the information the next time you look at our pages. 

SitemapX.com does not sell the information to advertisers, nor does it change your computer settings. You can also reset your browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when a cookie is sent, although doing this may interfere with the quality and speed of your browsing since some features won't work as they were meant to.
